

NAUSHIKHA JAYAWICKRAMA

Phone: +94 76331 6991 E-mail: hello@naushikha.com Website: naushikha.com







A GAME CHANGER.

PROFILE

Hardworking, self-motivated ambitious programmer with a keen eye for detail. Excellent track record of performance in all tasks undertaken with exceeding 4 years of cumulative industrial experience in fields such as game development and testing. Aiming to work in a challenging but friendly environment with a goal to become a part of a team. Primary interest is in computer graphics.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

SimCentric Technologies (Oct 2021 - May 2022)

• Working on <u>SAF-TAC</u>: a virtual reality based tactical military simulator.

PLAYTESTER

Arimac (Jan 2021 - May 2021)

• Testing and evaluating Android mobile games.

SYSTEM ENGINEER

Telasis Solutions (2017 - 2019)

- System and network installation and administration.
- Server and desktop hardware configuration.

PROJECTS

WHEN ONCE THE SKYWAS BLUE

Immersive 360° Web Experience - 2021

- Designed using Three.js, pure HTML, CSS and JS.
- Built to showcase at the Women's Theatre Festival '21- "WTFRINGE21".
- Completed entire experience within a short span of 2 weeks.
- Won the award for "Outstanding Visual Design".
 Trailer Link | Award Link | Review Link | Request for Demo

TEST ARENA

3D First Person Shooter - 2017

- Designed using Visual Basic 6.0, DirectX 8 and TrueVision3D.
- Personal project to explore boundaries of VB6 + TV3D.
 Write-up Link | Demo Video | Unity Remake (2021)

COMMAND ATTACK 3

3D First Person Shooter - 2012

- Designed using Visual Basic 6.0, DirectX 8 and TrueVision3D.
- Built to showcase at the "Anada Abhiman" exhibition of Ananda College.
- Completed 2 levels for the game in 2 weeks, including story, cutscenes and gameplay mechanics.
 Write-up Link

SKILLSET

Game Development

- Unreal Engine with C++.
- Unity with C#.

3D Web Experience Design

Using Three.js and pure HTML, CSS and JS.

EDUCATION

BSC (HONS)
COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Colombo School of Computing (2019 >>)

• Current GPA: 3.8 (out of 4.0)